(Leonard:)Afraid so, Skippy.
(Sheldon:)I told you we shouldn't
go shopping at night.
(Leonard:)All right, let's
all just calm down.
(Leonard:)Nobody wants to
report anybody.
(Man:)No, I don't like this.
I'm out.
(Leonard:)No, no, no. Wait, don't go.
(Leonard:)Just let me explain.
(Leonard:)We're physicists,
and we're trying to prove
(Leonard:)a hypothesis that we've been
working on for over a year.
(Man:)Really? What's the hypothesis?
(Sheldon:)Space-time can be interpreted as
(Sheldon:)the surface of
an n-dimensional superfluid.
(Man:)Hmm. Could be, could be.
(Man:)Go on.
(Leonard:)Okay, but now there's this
Swedish team that read our paper
(Leonard:)and they're trying to beat us
to our own discovery.
(Leonard:)We really need this helium.
(Sheldon:)And I'm sorry
I lied about
(Sheldon:)being a wedding planner
who can't find love.
(Sheldon:)Although I am currently
single, if you know anybody.
(Leonard:)Here's the money.
Can we do this?
(Stuart:)Okay.